Azime Nail

Riverside, New Jersey, United States



azimeznail@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/azime-nail

Summary

I am Turkish and American. After graduating high school in the United States, I received my Bachelor's degree in Psychology from Hacettepe University in Turkey. As of 2019, I'm back in the United States. I have experience in teaching English as a second language and now I have a certificate from Rutgers Bootcamp for Full Stack Flex Web Development.

Experience



🕝 Native English Teacher

Gi Group

Apr 2019 - Jul 2019 (4 months)

I gave one on one English lessons to employees of the company Leoni. I had 25 students and they each had 1.5 hours of lessons every week. I gave different lessons, depending on the student's level of English. Some needed writing practice, some needed speaking practice.

Native Teacher

Wall Street English Jun 2017 - Jun 2018 (1 year 1 month)

Student Helper

Hacettepe Üniversitesi Öğretim Elemanı Yetiştirme Programı Koordinatörlüğü May 2016 - Jun 2016 (2 months)

Research Assistant

Social Psychology Lab. May 2014 - Jun 2016 (2 years 2 months)

Research Intern

HÜPAM

Mar 2015 - Dec 2015 (10 months)

Library Assistant

Pennsauken Library Apr 2012 - Jun 2012 (3 months)

Education



Rutgers Bootcamps

Certificate, Full Stack Web Development

Nov 2022 - Feb 2023

A 12-week program covering a wide range of programming languages and technologies: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, Handlebars.js, MySQL, MongoDB, and Git.

• Hacettepe University

Bachelor's degree, Psychology 2012 - 2016

Pennsauken High School

High School Diploma 2009 - 2012

Licenses & Certifications



Language Interpretation and Translation - Rutgers University

Skills

MAXQDA • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • jQuery • Bootstrap • Express.js • React.js • Node.js • Handlebars.js

Honors & Awards

20. Ulusal Psikoloji Öğrencileri Kongresi - Hasan Kalyoncu Üniversitesi Jul 2015

"Bir Değişim Öyküsü Psikoterapi"

- 18. Ulusal Psikoloji Öğrencileri Kongresi İzmir Ekonomi Üniversitesi Jul 2013
 "Kontrol"
- VII. Işık Savaşır Klinik Psikoloji Sempozyumu Hacettepe Üniversitesi May 2015
- Obsesif-Kompulsif Bozuklukta Kültürlerarası Çalışmalar ve Güncel Tedavi Yaklaşımları Hacettepe Üniversitesi
 Jan 2016